gofro.com 2016-12-30

# Privacy Policy

We value the trust you place in gofro.com. That's why we insist upon the highest standards for secure transactions and customer information privacy. Note: Our privacy policy is subject to change at any time without notice.

#### Collection of Personally Identifiable Information

We collect personally identifiable information (email address, name phone number, etc.) from you when you set up a free account with Gofro.com. While you can browse some sections of our site without being a registered member, certain activities (such as placing an order) do require registration. We do use your contact information to send you offers based on your previous orders and your interests.

#### Use of Demographic and Profile Data

We use personal information to provide the services you request. We use your personal information to troubleshoot problems; collect fees owed; measure interest in our products and services, inform you about online and offline offers and customize your experience. In our efforts to continually improve our product and service offerings, we collect and analyze demographic and profile data about our users' activity on our website. We identify and use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our website.

Cookies

A "cookie" is a small piece of information stored by a Web server on a Web browser so it can be later read back from that browser. Cookies are useful for enabling the browser to remember information specific to a given user. Gofro.com places both permanent and temporary cookies in your computer's hard drive. Gofro.com's cookies do not contain any of your personally identifiable information.

Through our mobile app, we may disclose to third party services certain personally identifiable information listed below:

  * information you provide us such as name, email, mobile phone number
  * information we collect as you access and use our service
  * including device information, location and network carrier

This information is shared with third party service providers so that we can:

  * personalize the app for you
  * perform behavioral analytics

#### Security Precautions

Our site has stringent security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. Whenever you change or access your account information, we offer the use of a secure server. Once your information is in our possession we adhere to strict security guidelines, protecting it against unauthorized access.

#### Choice/Opt-Out

GoFro.com provides all users with the opportunity to opt-out of receiving non-essential (promotional, marketing-related) communications from us on behalf of our partners, and from us in general, after setting up an account.

#### Questions?

Questions regarding this statement should be directed to the following address: contactus@gofro.com
